domainproperties.com 2007-12-30

# Namebrokers - premium domain names for sale

**Privacy Policy: Introduction**

This site is owned and operated by Namebrokers, Inc ("Namebrokers"). Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. Namebrokers respects each individual’s right to personal privacy and seeks foremost to build a relationship based solely on the commerce of domain names. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This statement applies solely to information collected at the Namebrokers Website.

**Part I.   Information Collection **

Namebrokers gathers the following types of information about users:

  * Any information given to us by users that contact us via the inquiry form. These are voluntary submissions to receive further information. 
  * The email address and personal information from the visitors who communicate with us via email.
  * Aggregate (General Tracking) information about pages that users visit on our site.

Domain Offer: When you submit an offer for a domain name listed on our site through the online offer form, Namebrokers collects data that may include, but is not limited to, the following information: your full name, e-mail address, street address, phone and fax number. This information is used to contact the user with a counteroffer or confirmation of acceptance of their offer. 

Domain Purchase: When you agree to purchase a domain name listed on our site through the online purchase form, Namebrokers collects data that may include, but is not limited to, the following information: your full name, e-mail address, street address, phone and fax number. This information is used to complete the sales transaction. 

We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. Cookies enable Namebrokers to track usage patterns and deliver customized content to users. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser.

**Part II.   Information Usage. **

The information collected by Namebrokers will be used for internal review and contacting only.  Aggregate information that does not identify any individual may be used for the purpose of customizing site content. 

Namebrokers uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience on our site, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the site or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users. 

We offer links to other Web sites.  Please note: When you click on links to other Web sites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies.  Their standards may differ from ours.

**Part III.   Information Sharing. **

Namebrokers will not share any personal information given on the site (including name, email, or address) with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process. Namebrokers reserves to right to cooperate with any law agencies where improprieties occur and to provide information to such agencies including electronic correspondences and full customer records.

**Part IV.   Consent.**

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Namebrokers. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Namebrokers reserves the right to update this privacy policy at any time.

If you have any comments with regards to this privacy policy, please contact us.
